(Penny:)He spent the entire night...
(Penny:)...bragging about how he invented
the word "appeteasers."
[LEONARD CHUCKLING]
(Leonard:)How is that my fault?
(Penny:)You have destroyed my ability
to tolerate idiots.
(Penny:)Now, come with me.
(Leonard:)-Where are we going?
-We're gonna have sex.
LEONARD:
Why? I mean, okay.
(Penny:)What's going on?
Put on your noise-canceling headphones,
because it's gonna get loud.
Ugh. Not this again.
In what universe is this "low-pulp"?
(Sheldon:)Good morning, Penny.
(Penny:)Do you have eyes
in the back of your head?
(Sheldon:)When one gets beaten up
every other day in school...
(Sheldon:)...one, of necessity,
develops a keen sense of hearing.